my brother is older by five minutes and
apparently those five minutes gave him
the ability to succeed in life
[Laughter]
cuz that is that's the case for most
twins usually the overspending sells
everything by justice Mitch and mrs.
Chui seems like this is true you
struggle with this you probably gets
better grades and stuff you want the
same school so that's good right yeah
you hang on hang in there alright buddy
baby keep believing yeah my brothers
bear everything a better grades in
school better of sports this goes back
to birth this is true all this is true
my parents didn't know that I was coming
yeah they weren't expecting me about
they're just havin my brother that's
awesome
I crashed my own birth thank you guys
we're smelling birth right so that's no
good so my brother comes out like oh
look at a little baby we love him
it's got success his eyes is our fella
they put him in a nice warm cozy blanket
and this is what the doctor said word
for word cuz his story is so true I mean
so far everything is true it's so funny
who's told it every Thanksgiving dinner
the doctor said he said wait there's
something more there's something more
like I'm some beast or creature of
unknown species our origin that's a
licensed physician saying there's
something more like what why don't you
say longer maybe that's him after birth
that is taking human form
[Applause]
I kissed my brother's wrapped up a nice
warm cozy blanket they put me in a
bedpan that was my it's my welcome mat
to the world was a bedpan alike how
frizzy frizzy let me get some gauze or
something anything you people ask creepy
questions let's but guys this guy's ask
creepy questions guys ever ask if you
keep the old switch to room with your
girlfriend brother's girlfriend never
got that I get that quite what's that
but you did why'd you say no you never
did well of course you did because
you're not a sociopath good for you
Sammy we believe in you Sammy that's
right no judgment does not judge me here
you guys no judgment
I know it's a crazy thing like can you
imagine that scenario I'm like like my
brother's girlfriend doesn't know that
I'm shooting some ham and let's make it
out there I'm like huh huija sold
switcheroo
psychotic we're no worse days of my life
my brother and I played football in high
school right at end of the season that's
right guys I played football check it
out that was 5-7 150 pretty much
unstoppable you know I mean and at the
end of the season they give it the
awards tell the players he got all the
awards he was captain the football team
I wasn't he was MVP broke the rushing
record as a running back got
all-conference you know I got I got a
cute little certificate up his paper it
said honorable mention you guys are free
play with that that's it you know that
means basically means nice try Rudy
that's what that should say on a good
hustle good hustle loser find your
friend Lucas and play with bugs okay
because you're a nerd guys see the movie
Lucas so mate is this long time ago so
let's focus we're rocking out my
brother's got all these trophies and the
warts I've got this stupid piece of bark
with calligraphy on I just feeling
worthless the tension stick my step my
almost art made me feel better she's
like wow shell that's great we should
have that framed I'm like yeah that's a
great idea one day we'll frame that poop
on my wall here involved by failures and
shortcomings in life it'll be great
but Rex and Alan was that once a DUI
Nana was good one Chile blue two point
six
it's not gonna do that you guys that's
not good
it's about it what about this 890 what's
that that's your combined SAT score
that's it's a really bad scored he does
even take SATs in the or it's a CTS
isn't it Pacey T's what's a good score
for the a cts okay I got 23 that's not
good either
I here's what I always say we ever talk
to someone that takes this test like
they're like oh I don't I don't score
well on a serious test and she's not my
thing I don't score well in stand right
it's like it's such a cop-out is that
really who is it the number-2 pencil the
bubbles that disrupt their linear
thought patterns subscribe to drive our
comedy for even more of the world's
largest collection of clean comedy